[Music]
hi there my name is manav sin and you
would have seen me in some of the videos
at the auto YouTube channel if you're
someone who follows our content
regularly and if you're new well just
wait and watch what we have in store for
you today is going to blow your mind it
certainly did for me well before
rambling on let me tell you this is my
first year here at autox and I've always
been told that there comes one day when
we test some cars and speaking of which
if you would take a look at the Horizon
you'll see there's a long list of cars
that extends all the way to there and
and well I've been put to the task to
walk you through each and every one of
[Music]
them from the de is a miracle do making
them dance we about to change the game
we out here taking name let our voices
rise so with a big breath I'm going to
start off this journey and of course
we're going to start off with the heavy
hitter right here this ladies and
gentlemen if you haven't guessed already
is the lamp lambini Urus performante yes
it looks like an SUV but it will put
some of the sports cars to shame that's
what the promise this car holds and I'm
very excited to get my hands on this car
along with an esteemed panel of jewelry
who will drive all of the cars that you
see in this
video so yes that's the Lamborghini Urus
performante and right next to it as well
another SUV something with the theme of
of what we do here at autox this is the
porsa cayen again it looks like an SUV
but has sporty characteristics in its
bones both of these cars the Urus and
the Cayenne defy the expectations that
you have from SUVs and tell you the
sports cars maybe aren't dead yet but of
course we're talking about
SUVs and that is what we have here in
the classic definition this is a Lexus
LX if big bold muscular is what comes to
your mind when you think of an SUV well
that is precisely what it is I mean look
at just how it stands next to the other
cars that we've shown you this is as SUV
As It Gets In the conventional sense of
course but saving the day for sedan
lovers is the BMW i7 yes it's electric
but this is BMW's electric take on what
a sedan should be and they say that it
should be Electric and it should be this
yes it's got the tunes from Han Zimmer
to calm your mind but you won't be able
to keep your mind calm if you're seated
in one of these this is a properly fast
car loaded to the Bim with technology
but it's here to compete against a long
Lord which reminds me I should speed
this
up what's next to it is the mercedesbenz
eqv and what's next to it is the
mercedesbenz eqb now these two SUVs are
competing in the electric SUV space and
what they bring with themselves as well
premiumness at two different levels mind
you as you can see here one it's a
little bit more sensible and the other
one gives you the full flared magic of
Mercedes-Benz electric cars however if
you're someone who wants a conventional
luxury Mercedes-Benz GLC what you have
is this the new GLC big shoes to fill
but I hear they've done a rather well
job but the real test for this car is
here today because as you can see the
lineup is Big I'm going to keep saying
that multiple times in this video isn't
it nevertheless the GLC already a very
successful car just how far has
Mercedes-Benz pushed the limit well
we're going to find that out now again
continuing with the theme of SUVs it
doesn't get more Grand than the jeap
Grand Cheroke and I mean look at it you
wouldn't want this car in your rear view
mirror would you absolutely fantastic it
grows on you the more time you spend
with it and it of course being a Jeep
packs a whole lot of capabilities more
than a lot of cars that you can buy in
India
today next to it is a car that brings
practicality with value for money this
is a Toyota Innova High cross Ross a new
gen take on what the Innova stands for
and of course Innova is something that
you see on the road every day and now
that the new one is here we have to find
out just how good it has become of
course when it comes to seating a lot of
people in comfort for long distances
Inova is a household name this is the
high cross and we're going to see just
how good it has become now speaking of
Toyota well they've also stepped into a
new segment this year which is the
pickup truck now a lot of people a lot
of you guys love pickup trucks and the
hux is absolutely there at the top of
the list of cars that we always wanted
to see in India and it's finally come
here doesn't it look fantastic but
putting it to the test at the toac might
not be that cool but it's the hux once
it goes on the tox all a matter of fact
wherever it goes it makes itself the
coolest car that you have in your vision
and I I can say that it still stands
true now what you might not have seen
behind the hux is this the mg Comet once
you see it you cannot unsee it because
it's really cute it's electric it has
practicality on the top of its priority
list and an aggressive price tag is what
you get with the comet Eevee on paper it
sounds like the formula for success but
is it too compact well we are in the
perfect testing grounds I would say next
to it is the Tata Thiago Eevee arguably
the car that it's competing against and
perhaps the car that took electric car
to the masses the Thiago EV has been a
success with a lot of people a lot of
people love this car it falls with the
right price the right price segment the
right size and that formula is what
Citron is also trying to do with the
Citron EC3 so you get a theme Here If
You have about 10 12 lak rupees you have
three electric cars with very different
approaches
we're going to see what they really
stand for and if they're cutting any
corners and perhaps we'll find out if
India is ready for the electric
Revolution or maybe it's already
here because the electric cars don't end
we also have the Mahindra XUV 400 now
this one I would say stands in a
slightly different League because it
packs in a lot of performance it might
look understated here but when you put
the pedal to the metal this car will
shoot off into the Horizon I'm really
excited to spend more time with this
car next to it is the Mahindra tar it
might not look very different from the
Mahindra that you're used to that's
because there is practically not much
different this is the rear wheeel drive
variant which looks exactly the same but
it drives quite differently than the 4x4
tar the question is is this really a tar
well that's a question that needs to be
answered what we have here is a car that
you may have seen before like a couple
of cars ago well don't be confused this
is an Toyota Innova High cross but from
the house of maruti Suzuki that's the
partnership these two brands have today
and we get quite similar cars with
slightly different touches and that's
why we have the Innova High cross and
also the maruti Suzuki invictor but why
this is very important is because this
is the most expensive mati Suzuki that
you can buy in the country so obviously
this is the best mati Suzuki that money
can buy but is it enough for you to
spend that kind of money well it does
have the Inova underpinnings but maybe
it needs a bit more or not is what we're
going to find out this here is a citrin
C3 aircross yes the aircross name now
comes with C3 as well what's the Citron
is trying to do with the C3 I cross is
compete in a heavily competitive segment
their task is cut out they have got a
lot of things right and that includes an
aggressive price tag but is this going
to be enough well a lot of people would
say it definitely has made the cut to be
a contender for the best of 2023 here at
autox
awards perhaps its biggest rival is
right next to it as this is the Kia SOS
now the SOS is already a proven name a
proven car lot of sales lot of success
it was the first car that brought Kia to
the Indian market the SOS of course
holds a lot of importance so what Kia
has done is that they've taken a
conservative approach in order to bring
you the new cells they've not changed
what's not broken but they've added a
big list of features and safety Tech as
well when it comes to Conventional
approaches what you will not see at all
in a car is this this is the MAOI Suzuki
jimy finally it's come to our shes a lot
of people wanted this car to come to
India it's here it's bright it stands
out it gets the job done this is a car
that a lot of Judy members will be
fighting for the keys of and that
obviously includes me as well now coming
to the topic of speed the Volvo C40
recharge on the face of it it's not a
lot different
perhaps it's the xc40 but it does get
different Battery Technology different
motor tuning more range and offer and a
very good looking rear end with that
Coupe roof line double spoilers it's got
a lot of things that suggest this is a
fast car and it is it's frighteningly
quick this is a car that could upset the
competition when it comes to Pure
Performance what we have here is the
Lexus RX the RX is a well-known name
once again from the house of Lexus and
what it is is a bet at the middle of Two
Worlds combustion engines and electric
this is a hybrid is this the correct
answer for today if you're fighting for
making a decision between petrol and
electric well this is what we have to
find that answer with next to it is the
Honda elevate a lot of people have been
sending their questions about the car a
lot of questions will be answered today
the Honda helate is a mighty important
car for Honda cars India and if the
first impressions of the car in the
market or anything to go by this is
already on its way to become a success
but is it the best of
2023 that's a big
[Applause]
question what's next to it is the mati
Suzuki franx which may be a balino Under
the Skin but it does not look anything
like it and that's not a bad thing at
all because I think the franx is a very
good looking car the coupet shape
compact dimensions in your face styling
I love what mati Suzuki is doing these
days with the likes of the jimney and
the frogs it's really
exciting next up is the BMW X1 the entry
point into the BMW family of SUVs it's
bigger it's more feature loaded and I
would say it looks much better too and
speaking of premium SUVs we also have
the Audi Q3 which has caught up to the
times and is a very promising car in
today's day and age speaking of
promising cars well we have the Hyundai
warna in this lovely red shade
turbocharged 160 horsepower now this is
a car that's packed to the brim with
promise of fighting for the best of 2023
really excited to see how this sedan
pans out we did a good long comp
comparison test and this one came out on
the top amongst its beers and it's made
its way here as the best of 2023
condent next to it is the another
Hyundai the Hyundai EXA this is one of
the most competitively priced car here
lot of Promise once again I think it has
a design that does divide opinions but
when it comes to Pure value practicality
and good City performance
the extra is one of the best packages
that you can buy in this side of the 10
lakh rupe price segment so of course it
finds itself a
spot last but not the least well it's
been a long walk along all these
cars and it has all come to this the
Hyundai ionic 5 it's difficult to wrap
your head around what this car has to
offer it may look like a hatchback in
the pictures but it's a lot bigger but
at the end of the day what it is is an
EV unlike any other that you can buy a
Hyundai badge on such an expensive car
well I think the ionic more than
justifies it and it's got a lot of
performance on its side as well so on
the face of it it's a complete complete
package and speaking of complete well
what's complete is our walk through of
our lineup for the best of 2023 as you
can see it is a long lineup of cars it's
a long walk that I've just done and
that's a lot of words that I've just
spoken but that's still not enough
because packing in the best of 2023
contenders in this short of a time well
it's a tough task but what's not going
to be tough is finding out the best of
2023 as I said because we have some
really exciting cars and if you can't
make out which one I'm going to drive
first well you'll find out soon stay
tuned to our Auto YouTube channel we
will be telling you what our pick was
how the process went and we will award
the best of
2023 stay tuned and thank you very
[Music]
much